[
  {
    "type": "visitors-list",
    "dates": [
      {
        "date": "2017-02-12",
        "items": [
          { "time":"1486933916", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 1:11pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.143.129.107", "uid":"1446025430", "session_id":"491367853", "actions":"4", "total_visits":"43", "first_visit": {"time":"1484167141", "session_id":"442516692"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/education-networks-of-america/varmour-protects-student-information-at-education-networks-of-america", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1280x800", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"San Rafael, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.9719", "longitude":"-122.5023", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491367853"},
          { "time":"1486931536", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 12:32pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.213.2.5", "uid":"4255693985", "session_id":"491323563", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486910159", "session_id":"490921091"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Oakland, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7393", "longitude":"-122.1747", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491323563"},
          { "time":"1486930994", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 12:23pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"162.244.214.26", "uid":"2733425333", "session_id":"491313480", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486923836", "session_id":"491171429"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Foresthill, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.0361", "longitude":"-120.8291", "organization":"Sebastian", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491313480"},
          { "time":"1486929652", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 12pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"71.71.194.239", "uid":"3832651554", "session_id":"491287576", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1485355853", "session_id":"464480741"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Charlotte, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.2180", "longitude":"-80.7859", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491287576"},
          { "time":"1486929585", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 11:59am", "time_total":"262", "ip_address":"96.232.108.17", "uid":"1065721332", "session_id":"491286129", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486929585", "session_id":"491286129"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1280x800", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://tpc.googlesyndication.com/", "referrer_domain":"tpc.googlesyndication.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Briarcliff Manor, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.1468", "longitude":"-73.8318", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491286129"},
          { "time":"1486929155", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 11:52am", "time_total":"44", "ip_address":"47.23.16.254", "uid":"4130273026", "session_id":"491277559", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486866600", "session_id":"490418598"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 56.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Chinese", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"West Babylon, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7066", "longitude":"-73.3501", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491277559"},
          { "time":"1486928525", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 11:42am", "time_total":"238", "ip_address":"174.238.12.120", "uid":"1953782898", "session_id":"491265014", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1485824973", "session_id":"472802644"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Peoria, Arizona, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5806", "longitude":"-112.2374", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491265014"},
          { "time":"1486927266", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 11:21am", "time_total":"300", "ip_address":"107.77.224.172", "uid":"4033751910", "session_id":"491239650", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486927266", "session_id":"491239650"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 56.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8596", "longitude":"-73.9314", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491239650"},
          { "time":"1486926880", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 11:14am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"195.142.179.4", "uid":"835642409", "session_id":"491231675", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486915282", "session_id":"491011365"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"Turkish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Antalya, Turkey", "country_code":"tr", "latitude":"36.9081", "longitude":"30.6956", "hostname":"superonline.net", "organization":"Solnet", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491231675"},
          { "time":"1486923836", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 10:23am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"70.211.76.57", "uid":"2733425333", "session_id":"491171429", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486923836", "session_id":"491171429"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rocklin, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.8052", "longitude":"-121.2453", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491171429"},
          { "time":"1486921144", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 9:39am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"64.201.202.24", "uid":"33857467", "session_id":"491119234", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486921144", "session_id":"491119234"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Regina, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"50.4153", "longitude":"-104.6103", "hostname":"sasknet.sk.ca", "organization":"Sasktel", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491119234"},
          { "time":"1486920126", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 9:22am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"72.208.182.139", "uid":"3955123908", "session_id":"491100121", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486920126", "session_id":"491100121"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 56.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1600x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.com/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.com", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"search", "geolocation":"Scottsdale, Arizona, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.6119", "longitude":"-111.8906", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491100121"},
          { "time":"1486919390", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 9:09am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.232.152", "uid":"3049432248", "session_id":"491086417", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486919390", "session_id":"491086417"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8596", "longitude":"-73.9314", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491086417"},
          { "time":"1486918488", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:54am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"72.159.38.19", "uid":"3772786610", "session_id":"491069784", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486918488", "session_id":"491069784"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Bardstown, Kentucky, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7905", "longitude":"-85.4848", "hostname":"bardstown.com", "organization":"At&t Internet Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491069784"},
          { "time":"1486918480", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:54am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"71.167.158.178", "uid":"3236055189", "session_id":"491069671", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486918480", "session_id":"491069671"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brooklyn, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6643", "longitude":"-73.9150", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491069671"},
          { "time":"1486918442", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:54am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"99.247.80.146", "uid":"1223070042", "session_id":"491068949", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486918442", "session_id":"491068949"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ottawa, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"45.2691", "longitude":"-75.7518", "hostname":"rogers.com", "organization":"Rogers Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491068949"},
          { "time":"1486918350", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:52am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"142.169.78.92", "uid":"2597754990", "session_id":"491067147", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486918350", "session_id":"491067147"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Montr√©al, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"45.5000", "longitude":"-73.5833", "organization":"Telus Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491067147"},
          { "time":"1486918058", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:47am", "time_total":"162", "ip_address":"71.71.194.239", "uid":"3832651554", "session_id":"491061585", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1485355853", "session_id":"464480741"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Charlotte, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.2180", "longitude":"-80.7859", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491061585"},
          { "time":"1486917686", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:41am", "time_total":"579", "ip_address":"201.171.195.76", "uid":"757397855", "session_id":"491054937", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486917686", "session_id":"491054937"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"Chinese", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mexicali, Mexico", "country_code":"mx", "latitude":"32.6519", "longitude":"-115.4683", "hostname":"telnor.net", "organization":"Telefonos Del Noroeste, S.a. De C.v.", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491054937"},
          { "time":"1486917621", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:40am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"138.197.96.201", "uid":"2615830584", "session_id":"491053705", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486917621", "session_id":"491053705"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Firefox 28.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7214", "longitude":"-74.0052", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491053705"},
          { "time":"1486917478", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:37am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.199.197.169", "uid":"2615997321", "session_id":"491051051", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486917478", "session_id":"491051051"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Firefox 50.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Roanoke, Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.2701", "longitude":"-79.9601", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491051051"},
          { "time":"1486916796", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:26am", "time_total":"59", "ip_address":"69.118.137.153", "uid":"1834389314", "session_id":"491038519", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486916796", "session_id":"491038519"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brooklyn, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.5961", "longitude":"-73.9732", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491038519"},
          { "time":"1486916749", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:25am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"67.20.27.46", "uid":"2504219408", "session_id":"491037621", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486916749", "session_id":"491037621"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Lawton, Oklahoma, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.6266", "longitude":"-98.3434", "hostname":"fidnet.com", "organization":"Fidelity Communication International", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491037621"},
          { "time":"1486916350", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:19am", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"68.42.146.213", "uid":"704388546", "session_id":"491030615", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486916350", "session_id":"491030615"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Clarkston, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.7237", "longitude":"-83.4222", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491030615"},
          { "time":"1486916082", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:14am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.195.87.4", "uid":"3349655209", "session_id":"491025806", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486916082", "session_id":"491025806"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chesterfield, Missouri, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.6631", "longitude":"-90.5771", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491025806"},
          { "time":"1486915840", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:10am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.194.1.177", "uid":"2696863552", "session_id":"491021485", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486913052", "session_id":"490971551"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Waterford, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.6884", "longitude":"-83.3865", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491021485"},
          { "time":"1486915593", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:06am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"70.32.217.59", "uid":"1453158278", "session_id":"491016996", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486915593", "session_id":"491016996"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Clarksburg, West Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.2824", "longitude":"-80.3687", "hostname":"ntelos.net", "organization":"Ntelos Commuications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491016996"},
          { "time":"1486915300", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:01am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"97.64.160.28", "uid":"2589768446", "session_id":"491011693", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486911081", "session_id":"490937136"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Peosta, Iowa, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.4245", "longitude":"-90.8083", "hostname":"mchsi.com", "organization":"Mediacom Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491011693"},
          { "time":"1486915282", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8:01am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"188.57.34.38", "uid":"835642409", "session_id":"491011365", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486915282", "session_id":"491011365"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"Turkish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Izmir, Turkey", "country_code":"tr", "latitude":"38.4127", "longitude":"27.1384", "organization":"Turkcell", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491011365"},
          { "time":"1486915215", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 8am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"128.177.161.161", "uid":"2170320969", "session_id":"491010033", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486915215", "session_id":"491010033"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"San Jose, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.3874", "longitude":"-121.9024", "organization":"Jasper Technologies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491010033"},
          { "time":"1486915166", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:59am", "time_total":"31", "ip_address":"184.151.231.36", "uid":"2086857354", "session_id":"491009199", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486915166", "session_id":"491009199"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Vancouver, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"49.2559", "longitude":"-123.1322", "organization":"Bell Mobility", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491009199"},
          { "time":"1486915083", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:58am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.26.110.166", "uid":"3482668370", "session_id":"491007711", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486915083", "session_id":"491007711"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Orleans, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"45.4697", "longitude":"-75.4715", "hostname":"bell.ca", "organization":"Bell Canada", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491007711"},
          { "time":"1486914971", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:56am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"216.8.238.194", "uid":"1893170794", "session_id":"491005492", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486914971", "session_id":"491005492"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brookville, Indiana, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.4047", "longitude":"-84.9736", "hostname":"etczone.com", "organization":"Enhanced Telecommunications Corp.", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491005492"},
          { "time":"1486914818", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:53am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"173.81.227.44", "uid":"2597635577", "session_id":"491002884", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486914818", "session_id":"491002884"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 56.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Charleston, West Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.4825", "longitude":"-81.6447", "hostname":"suddenlink.net", "organization":"Suddenlink Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491002884"},
          { "time":"1486914695", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:51am", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"166.182.82.118", "uid":"3894931472", "session_id":"491000493", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486911136", "session_id":"490938056"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "organization":"Wireless Data Service Provider Corporation", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=491000493"},
          { "time":"1486913585", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:33am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"64.134.35.175", "uid":"3367723412", "session_id":"490980773", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486913585", "session_id":"490980773"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"wayport.net", "organization":"At&t Wi-fi Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490980773"},
          { "time":"1486913115", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:25am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.42.230.209", "uid":"2272567929", "session_id":"490972686", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486913115", "session_id":"490972686"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Statesboro, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.3729", "longitude":"-81.8443", "hostname":"frontiernet.net", "organization":"Frontier Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490972686"},
          { "time":"1486913052", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:24am", "time_total":"783", "ip_address":"70.194.1.177", "uid":"2696863552", "session_id":"490971551", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486913052", "session_id":"490971551"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Waterford, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.6884", "longitude":"-83.3865", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490971551"},
          { "time":"1486912703", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:18am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"76.222.70.243", "uid":"3415926882", "session_id":"490965486", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486912703", "session_id":"490965486"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Depere, Wisconsin, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"44.3906", "longitude":"-88.0310", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490965486"},
          { "time":"1486912385", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:13am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.164.18", "uid":"103779096", "session_id":"490959932", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486912385", "session_id":"490959932"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490959932"},
          { "time":"1486911928", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:05am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.188.133.22", "uid":"3487748342", "session_id":"490952026", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486911250", "session_id":"490940058"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Shirley, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7948", "longitude":"-72.8797", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490952026"},
          { "time":"1486911694", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 7:01am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.195.87.4", "uid":"407148745", "session_id":"490947826", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486911694", "session_id":"490947826"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chesterfield, Missouri, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.6631", "longitude":"-90.5771", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490947826"},
          { "time":"1486911275", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:54am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"45.19.168.41", "uid":"4021905151", "session_id":"490940477", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486911275", "session_id":"490940477"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPod", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Toledo, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.6024", "longitude":"-83.6337", "organization":"At&t Internet Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490940477"},
          { "time":"1486911250", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:54am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.188.133.22", "uid":"3487748342", "session_id":"490940058", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486911250", "session_id":"490940058"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Shirley, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7948", "longitude":"-72.8797", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490940058"},
          { "time":"1486911136", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:52am", "time_total":"119", "ip_address":"166.182.80.118", "uid":"3894931472", "session_id":"490938056", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486911136", "session_id":"490938056"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "organization":"Wireless Data Service Provider Corporation", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490938056"},
          { "time":"1486911081", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:51am", "time_total":"243", "ip_address":"97.64.160.28", "uid":"2589768446", "session_id":"490937136", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486911081", "session_id":"490937136"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Peosta, Iowa, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.4245", "longitude":"-90.8083", "hostname":"mchsi.com", "organization":"Mediacom Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490937136"},
          { "time":"1486910449", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:40am", "time_total":"298", "ip_address":"113.203.62.153", "uid":"4181084418", "session_id":"490925967", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486910449", "session_id":"490925967"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"The United Arab Emirates", "country_code":"ae", "latitude":"24.0000", "longitude":"54.0000", "organization":"Salar Llc Fze", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490925967"},
          { "time":"1486910431", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:40am", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"173.61.40.172", "uid":"327086217", "session_id":"490925649", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486910431", "session_id":"490925649"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Salem, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.5317", "longitude":"-75.4376", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490925649"},
          { "time":"1486910281", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:38am", "time_total":"602", "ip_address":"174.200.10.123", "uid":"2260683775", "session_id":"490923213", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486910281", "session_id":"490923213"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Wilmington, Delaware, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.7472", "longitude":"-75.5918", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490923213"},
          { "time":"1486910159", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:35am", "time_total":"333", "ip_address":"73.170.192.165", "uid":"4255693985", "session_id":"490921091", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1486910159", "session_id":"490921091"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sonoma, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.2433", "longitude":"-122.4602", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490921091"},
          { "time":"1486909661", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:27am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.234.225", "uid":"3924000039", "session_id":"490912722", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486909661", "session_id":"490912722"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.7490", "longitude":"-84.3880", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490912722"},
          { "time":"1486909567", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:26am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"103.218.248.123", "uid":"380808342", "session_id":"490911229", "actions":"4", "total_visits":"16", "first_visit": {"time":"1481898836", "session_id":"403356867"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"600x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"17.3753", "longitude":"78.4744", "organization":"Satya Ratna Agencies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490911229"},
          { "time":"1486909394", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:23am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.164.31", "uid":"523948587", "session_id":"490908515", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486909394", "session_id":"490908515"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490908515"},
          { "time":"1486909328", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:22am", "time_total":"62", "ip_address":"162.218.4.188", "uid":"1162708768", "session_id":"490907404", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486909328", "session_id":"490907404"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Newington, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.5626", "longitude":"-81.4940", "hostname":"planters.net", "organization":"Planters Rural Telephone Cooperative", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490907404"},
          { "time":"1486909207", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:20am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"75.137.141.173", "uid":"2785204755", "session_id":"490905560", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486909207", "session_id":"490905560"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPod", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Hartselle, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.4436", "longitude":"-86.9369", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490905560"},
          { "time":"1486909154", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:19am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"97.84.17.244", "uid":"511406187", "session_id":"490904627", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486909154", "session_id":"490904627"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Northport, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.4235", "longitude":"-87.5580", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490904627"},
          { "time":"1486908584", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:09am", "time_total":"95", "ip_address":"173.73.15.228", "uid":"2356600950", "session_id":"490895630", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486908584", "session_id":"490895630"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Woodbridge, Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.6780", "longitude":"-77.3197", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490895630"},
          { "time":"1486908247", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:04am", "time_total":"713", "ip_address":"172.56.14.165", "uid":"1939523288", "session_id":"490890329", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486908247", "session_id":"490890329"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Houston, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.7633", "longitude":"-95.3633", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490890329"},
          { "time":"1486908177", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 6:02am", "time_total":"641", "ip_address":"174.194.20.127", "uid":"3111344714", "session_id":"490889267", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486908177", "session_id":"490889267"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490889267"},
          { "time":"1486899271", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 3:34am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"201.83.139.171", "uid":"3749040833", "session_id":"490767038", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"21", "first_visit": {"time":"1485803823", "session_id":"472370075"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Portuguese", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"S√£o Paulo, Brazil", "country_code":"br", "latitude":"-23.5475", "longitude":"-46.6361", "hostname":"virtua.com.br", "organization":"Net Virtua", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490767038"},
          { "time":"1486898119", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 3:15am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"138.197.111.17", "uid":"2535085997", "session_id":"490753633", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1486898119", "session_id":"490753633"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Firefox 28.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7214", "longitude":"-74.0052", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490753633"},
          { "time":"1486892218", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 1:36am", "time_total":"825", "ip_address":"107.77.196.109", "uid":"2055238077", "session_id":"490685977", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"13", "first_visit": {"time":"1486479390", "session_id":"484362744"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 51.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.7787", "longitude":"-96.8217", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490685977"},
          { "time":"1486892117", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 1:35am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.215.153", "uid":"2861246760", "session_id":"490684865", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"9", "first_visit": {"time":"1486568228", "session_id":"485748157"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fort Lauderdale, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"26.0681", "longitude":"-80.2766", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490684865"},
          { "time":"1486889198", "time_pretty":"Sun Feb 12 2017, 12:46am", "time_total":"203", "ip_address":"201.83.139.171", "uid":"3749040833", "session_id":"490652937", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"21", "first_visit": {"time":"1485803823", "session_id":"472370075"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Portuguese", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"S√£o Paulo, Brazil", "country_code":"br", "latitude":"-23.5475", "longitude":"-46.6361", "hostname":"virtua.com.br", "organization":"Net Virtua", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=490652937"}
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]